Viewers, we want to let you know that you are here; we are there.
Right now, open your lips and begin to declare God's faithfulness.
He is faithful to deliver you!
His faithfulness is so much - He has made a way for your healing!
He has made a way for your healing, for your deliverance.
Open your lips and begin to declare God's faithfulness.
No matter what you are going through - are you on the sickbed?
Are you on the sickbed?
Begin to declare God's faithfulness.
Declare God's faithfulness, in Jesus Christ's name we pray.
I command that deliverance on you, in the name of Jesus!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
These are the provisions God has provided already.
After declaring God's faithfulness, He has made a way for your deliverance.
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
He has made a way for your deliverance.
Viewers, as I pray, I sense God's healing touching you.
I sense God's deliverance;
I sense God's blessing.
Be ready; are you there?
In the name of Jesus!
Freedom!
Healing!
Deliverance!
Receive!
I lay my hand upon you.
I command healing, in the name of Jesus!
Healing to your body, in the name of Jesus!
Healing to your blood, in the name of Jesus!
Healing to your kidneys, in the name of Jesus!
Healing to your liver, in the name of Jesus!
Healing to your bones, in the name of Jesus!
Healing to your fluids, in the name of Jesus!
Healing to your blood, in the name of Jesus!
Wherever it is located, you affliction, move!
Leave my people!
In the name of Jesus!
Confess your healing!
Confess your freedom!
Confess your deliverance!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, begin to give thanks to God for giving you faith that you are set free -
faith to believe that you are free.
Give thanks to Him.
Give thanks to God.